mojotab.com 2018-01-08

# 

At mojotab.com, we respect your privacy, and we understand the importance of the information you entrust to us. This Privacy Policy describes the practices concerning the information collected by the MadX Services family of companies consisting MadX Services (“MadX Services”, "we", "us" and "our") and we provide this Privacy Policy so that our users ("you") will know what information is being collected about you and your activities on mojotab.com, how that information is being used, and with whom it is being shared. This Privacy Policy describes the online privacy practices applicable to the web pages within the Internet domain mojotab.com including all subdomains thereunder and specifically including any subdomain optimized for use on mobile devices ("mojotab.com" or the "Site") and the various services ("Site Services") we provide on or through the Site. 

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us. Unless indicated otherwise, the Site and Site Services are subject to our Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. If you install a “Search Application” for example applications, web search toolbars, browser or OS plug-ins, taskbars, desktop widgets, new tab/startpage products, search extensions and/or search settings extensions, mobile applications, including mobile widgets, mobile browsers, mobile launchers, mobile lock screens, and any or all that may be branded (or co-branded) with MadX Services, MadX Services-affiliate, or third party brands, or bear other brands owned by or licensed to MadX Services, content, products, and services controlled or operated by MadX Services, you will be subject to the End User License Agreement that describe what information we collect when you use the Search Application and how that information may be used. Certain services may be subject to different privacy policies and/or terms of service as indicated on the sites from where those services are available and/ or accessed. 

By using the Site and Site Services you consent to our collection and use of your data as described in this Privacy Policy. As our privacy practices evolve, we will update this privacy policy. Any material changes in our privacy practices will be posted prominently on this page. 

What types of information do we collect when you use the Site and Site Services? 

Each time you visit the Site, we collect the limited information that your browser makes available. This information includes: (a) your Internet Protocol (IP) address; (b) the address of the last URL you visited before clicking through to the Site; (c) your browser and platform type; (d) your browser language; and (e) the data in any undeleted "cookies" that your browser previously accepted from us (see "How are cookies used on the Site?" below). Additionally, when you enter a search query using the Site or Site Services, we will receive the query text and process it, together with the above data, to return a search results page to you. If you have modified your browser settings so that address-bar search queries and erroneous domain name system (DNS) requests are submitted to us, we may also receive any search query or misspelled URL that you enter into your browser's address bar. 

If you access the Site through a mobile device we may collect additional information including: (i) the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your mobile device; (ii) one way hashed device ID; (iii) your mobile device language; (iv) your mobile device OS (operating system); (v) your mobile device make and model; (vi) a new session on the Site; (v) the duration you spend on the Site; (vi) your clicks on ads or links in connection with the Site. 

If you access the Site through a Search Application, we may also collect information about that Search Application (eg. The specific release date and distribution source of your Search Application, a unique Search Application ID, Search Application partner ID, the ads you click on, and information contained in error log files or cookies, aggregate query or click data and erroneous domain name system requests). 

Some of the foregoing information may be collected via a third party (e.g., comScore) pixel or web beacon and/or information stored in cookies. We do not link the information we store in these cookies to any personally identifiable information. 

The Site and Site Services usually do not require registration or submission of an account name or email address in order to use them. However, we will collect your email address if you submit a help request to us via email. The amount of information that you choose to disclose to us is completely up to you. 

How may we use the information we collect? 

We use the information that we collect to facilitate the delivery of relevant and/or targeted search results, improve the overall quality of your experience with the Site and Site Services, and to facilitate evaluation, improvement, and development of the Site Services. We aggregate query information for internal reporting purposes and optimization of advertising revenue. We count, track, and aggregate our visitors' activities in our analysis of general traffic flows at the Site (e.g., tracking where users come from, what pages they select within the Site, how they interact with search results, etc.). 

Information about the search queries you submit to the Site and how you interact with search results may also be used to personalize the content and advertisements that we present to you. We may, based on the search queries you submit and the search results you select (including paid search results), draw inferences about your interests and display advertisements matched to such interests. You may receive such customized ads on the Site and on third-party sites (see also "What information do we share with third parties?" below). If you would like to terminate and Site's access to your search history you may remove our cookies from your computer (see "How are cookies used on the Site?" below and consult your browser's "help" menu to learn how to delete cookies). 

If you choose to submit your name, email address, or other information, we may use such information to contact you to respond to a request from you, or in connection with legal proceedings, or if there has been a violation of our Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy. We do not associate your search queries or selected search results in any manner with your name, email address, or other information, unless required to do so by legal process. 

How are cookies used on the Site? 

We use cookies and other technology such as pixel tags to track traffic flow and patterns of travel, to collect and store information in connection with the Site. Cookies are a standard Internet technology that allows us to store and retrieve information on a user's system. Our web server automatically asks a new user's browser whether it will accept our cookie file. Please see our Cookies Policy for further information about our use of these technologies. 

If the user's browser accepts our cookie, our web server will record the cookie's unique ID for our use in internal reporting and for customized advertising (see "How may we use the information we collect?" above). Some or all of your search queries and interactions with search results on the Site is associated with your unique cookie ID. When you use the Site we may use your cookie data to customize the Site Services and advertisements delivered to you (see "Data collection and sharing involving third parties" below). 

If you would like to remove our cookies from your computer, you can delete them using your browser (consult your browser's "help" menu to learn how to delete cookies). If you would like to remove our cookies from your mobile device, you should consult your mobile device privacy and the browser tabs in the "Settings" menu to learn how to change the settings on your mobile device and clear cookies. 

Major browsers provide users with various options when it comes to cookies. Users can usually set their browsers to block all third-party cookies (which are those set by third-party companies collecting information on websites operated by other companies), block all cookies (including first-party cookies such as the ones we use to collect search activity information about its users), or block specific cookies. To modify your cookie settings, please refer to the following support pages for each browser you use to access the Website: 

Internet Explorer help: http://windows.microsoft.com/en-GB/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11 Firefox help: http://kb.mozillazine.org/Cookies#Firefox Safari help: http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042 Chrome help: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en 

We do not use cookies to track your use of the Internet in any other way, or associate your name, email address, or personal information with your cookie data. We do not disclose cookie information to third parties, except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy (see "What information do we share with third parties?" below). 

Use of cookies on our Site by third parties. We use third-party companies to serve advertisements when you visit the Site. These companies may use information about your visits to the Site in order to present advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements on the Site, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as pixel tags in connection with the Site. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad-serving company might collect from you. These companies have their own recordkeeping and data-retention policies. If you would like to consider your options for limiting use of such information by advertising companies, or would like to learn more about this practice, please click here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/. We also use third party vendors to help us better understand our user demographics. These vendors may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as pixel tags in connection with the Site to provide their services to us. 

What information may we share with third parties? 

We do not share your name name, or email address or any other personal information with third parties for the purpose of enabling them to send you information about their products or services (or for any other purpose, except to respond to legal process as described below). 

Third-party service providers. Some elements or features of the Site, such as the sponsored results advertising on our Site pages, are supplied to us by one or more third parties under contract. Some elements or features of the Site, such as the sponsored results advertising on our Site pages, are supplied to us by one or more third parties under contract. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that third-party service providers might collect from you. These companies have their own recordkeeping and data-retention policies. 

We may supply some of the information we collect from you to those third parties so that they can provide those elements or features for display on the Site. Some of the information you input may be supplied directly to our service providers so they can provide some of the services and features in connection with our Site. In addition, we may share the following information with third parties: (a) your Internet Protocol (IP) address; (b) the address of the last URL you visited before clicking through to the Site; (c) your browser and platform type; (d) your browser language; (e) the data in any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us; (f) the search queries you submit; and/or (g) other information described in the "What types of information do we collect when you use the Site and Site Services" section of this policy above. For example, when you submit a query, we transmit it (and some of the related information described above) to our paid-listing providers in order to generate relevant advertising to display in response to your query and to optimize the number and quality of sponsored results that will be provided to you on the Site. We may merge information about you into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers. If you provide us with answers to voluntary survey questions, we may furnish this information to our advertisers and partners in the form of group statistics compiled from our users' answers to such questions. 

Search Partners. If you have accessed the Site through an MadX Services or third party application installed on your computer or mobile device, then our search partners that developed or distributed the search application may collect information about you including the queries you submit via our Site, the search application or your browser, as well as the search results and ads you click on and the address of the web pages you previously listed. 

We have agreements in place with our search partners and our third-party service providers that limits their use and disclosure of any information about you that you provide directly to us (i.e., information not provided directly by you to the applicable search partner or third-party service providers. 

Law enforcement/legal requirements. We may disclose any information you voluntarily submit to us, as well as any other information we have about you (such as your IP address, the search queries you have submitted, and the search results you have selected) in order to comply with court orders, subpoenas, or regulatory obligations, or when otherwise required to do so by law. We also may disclose such information in compliance with a law-enforcement or other governmental request, or where we believe disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of our Terms of Service. 

Corporate restructuring. We also may transfer your information to a third party if we or any of our affiliates are involved in a corporate restructuring (e.g., a sale, merger, or other transfer of assets). 

What happens when you leave the Site to go to other Internet sites? 

We do not control the information collection and dissemination policies of third-party companies. When you are on the Site, you may be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. For example, if you click on a search result, the click may take you to a third-party website. These other sites may independently collect data from or about you, solicit information from you, or place their own cookies on your computer. We are not responsible for any use of the information such third-party sites may collect. 

What is our policy regarding personally identifiable information from children under 13? 

Our Site and Site Services are intended for general audiences over the age of 13 years old. We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are not over 13 years old, DO NOT DOWNLOAD ANY SEARCH APPLICATION OR USE THE SITE, SERVICES OR SITE SERVICES. 

Do we take security precautions to protect your information? 

We have security measures in place that are designed to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to information we collect online. We utilize both industry and proprietary standards to preserve the confidentiality of information. We seek to limit access to our users' information to employees who we believe reasonably need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to perform their jobs. These employees have been informed of the need to maintain the security and confidentiality of such information. Unfortunately, no security system can be 100% secure; accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that we collect online. 

Do Not Track Signals. Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. DNT is a way for users to inform websites and services that they do not want certain information about their webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. 

We are committed to providing you with meaningful choices about the information collected on our website for third party purposes, and that is why we provide the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out link above. However, we do not recognize or respond to browser-initiated DNT signals that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer's online activities over time and across third-party Web sites or online services. 

If you would like to request the removal of a search result generated using your name as the search term, please send your request in writing to MadX Services at the email below. To assist us in processing your request in timely manner, please make your request in English if you are able to do so. Your request should include any information relevant to your request, including: (i) your name, email and postal address; (ii) the URL (i.e., “web address”) for each link that you are requesting to be removed; (iii) a brief explanation of why you believe such results should be removed; (iv) an explanation of whether or not you fulfill a role in public life; and (v) an explanation as to why the contents of the link you wish to have removed relate to you. 

To help us prevent fraudulent removal requests, please also include a legible copy of a document that verifies your identity. You need not provide a government-issued document; a utility bill or similar mailing will suffice. You may also obscure parts of the document such as identifying numbers so long as the document continues to clearly identify you. If you are requesting the removal of search results that contain photographs of you, please ensure that the identifying document includes your photograph. If you are making the request on behalf of another person, please indicate your relationship to that person and provide evidence of your authority to make such request. All requests for removal will be reviewed by MadX Services legal and compliance team in India and we reserve the right, in compliance with applicable laws and considering the balance between the user’s right to privacy and the public’s interest in access to information, to accept or reject, or make further inquiries regarding, any requests. 

Notice and Consent to Transfer of Information 

Information we collect may be transferred to, stored and processed in any country or territory where one or more of our affiliated group companies or third party service providers are located or maintain facilities, including but not limited to India. The data-protection and other laws in India and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your own country. Please be assured, however, that we seek to take reasonable steps to protect your privacy. By using the Site and Site Services, you consent to the transfer of your information to our facilities and those third parties with whom we may share it as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Reviewing, changing or deleting information 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, or if you would like to review, change or delete personal information we have collected from you, you can contact us via email at contact@madx.co. 

© 2016 MadX Services ® All rights reserved.
